Herold J. Wiens Collection
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Nanking by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1944., 128; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NI 50, "Nanking", 1st Edition-AMS 4; Copied from Survey of India dated 1941.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Fuchou by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 129; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NG 50, "Fuchou", 5th Edition-AMS 6; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Hong Kong by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 130; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NF 50, "Hong Kong", 5th Edition-AMS 5; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Hankow by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 131; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NH 50, "Hankow", 3rd Edition-AMS 4; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Mukden by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1944., 132; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NK 51, "Mukden", 1st Edition-AMS 1; Copied from Japanese Inperial Land Survey dated 1936.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Shanghai by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 133; 1 Map 660 x 810 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NK 51, "Shanghai", 3rd Edition-AMS 4; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.; Access Points: China
- Takla Makan Desert ONC-G-7 by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center. St. Louis, MO: United States. Air Force, 1963., 134; 1 Map 1060 x 1400 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Access Points: China, Kashmir
- World Aeronautical Chart. Tung-t'ing Lake by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center. St. Louis, MO: United States. Air Force, 1952., 135; 1 Map 560 x 735 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 494.; Access Points: China Tung-t'ing Lake
- World Aeronautical Chart. Hung-tse Lake by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center. St. Louis, MO: United States. Air Force, 1950., 136; 1 Map 560 x 735 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 386.; Access Points: China Hung-tse Lake
- World Aeronautical Chart. Hang-chou Bay by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center. St. Louis, MO: United States. Air Force, 1955., 137; 1 Map 560 x 735 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 492.; Access Points: China Hang-chou Bay
- World Aeronautical Chart. Wei River by United States. Air Force.Aeronautical Chart and Information Center. St. Louis, MO: United States. Air Force, 1951., 138; 1 Map 560 x 735 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Number 384.; Access Points: China Wei River
- China Physical by Haack H. Geographisch-Kartographische Anstalt, VEB, Gotha. East Germany: Haack H. Geographisch Kartographische,VEB Gotha, 1963., 139; 1 Map 1610 x 2160 cm.; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; Relief shown by gradient tints and shading.; Wall Map.; Access Points: China Japan
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Chieh-yang by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1946., 140; 1 Map 460 x 460 cm.; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Chieh-yang",Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photograpy,Central Land Survey 1937.; Access Points: China
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Hsia-men by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1946., 141; 1 Map 660 x 550 cm.; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Hsia-men", Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photograpy,Central Land Survey 1937.; Access Points: China
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Yung-chia by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 142; 1 Map 710 x 610 cm.; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Yung-chia", Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.; Access Points: China
- China City Plans 1:12,500. Fu-chou and Nan-tai by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 143; 1 Map 960 x 760 cm.; 1:12,500; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S.L901; Series sheets: "Fu-chou" and "Nan-t'ai", Type C-AMS 1; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.; Access Points: China
- Eastern China 1:50,000. Peking by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 144; 1 Map 560 x 760 cm.; 1:50,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. GSGS; Series sheets: Sheet 16/2,200, "Peking", 3rd Edition-AMS 3; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.; Access Points: China
- China 1:25,000. Hankow by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 145; 1 Map 960 x 680 cm.; 1:25,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. L1901; Series sheets: "Hankow", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from Aerial Photography and AMS Editions.; Access Points: China
- China Special Strategic Map. [Southeastern China] by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 146; 1 Map 660 x 760 cm.; 1:4,000,000; Lambert Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5207; Series sheets: "China", 3rd Edition,-AMS 3; Copied from Earlier AMS Editions.; Access Points: China
- Hong Kong and New Territory 1:80,000. by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 147; 1 Map 760 x 1060 cm.; 1: 80,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: GSGS 1938; Series sheets: "Hong Kong and New Territory", 2nd Edition-AMS 3; Copied from Earlier AMS Editions.; Access Points: China Hong Kong
- Outline Map 1:19,000,000. [China, Japan, Pacific Ocean, Australia] by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1943., 148; 1 Map 1060 x 710 cm.; 1:19,000,000; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 1101; Series sheets: "Outline Map", Sheet No. 3; Copied from 1933 Municipal Plan.; Access Points: China Japan
- Plan of Shanghai (Sheet 1) 1:15,840. by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States, Army, 1945., 149; 1 Map 700 x 1060 cm.; 1:15,840; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: GSGS 3956; Access Points: China
- China Transportation 1:2,750,000. by United States Foreign Economic Administration. Maps and Graphics Division, F.E.A., June 15, 1945., 150; 1 Map 1080 x 880 cm.; 1:2,750,000; Format: Map; Map series: N0. 1379; Access Points: China
- China, Seen From the Direction of Guam by From Magazine [unknown]., 151; 1 Map 360 x 570 cm; Format: Map; Access Points: China
- Jan Jan's Map of Kowloon by Jan Jan Publishing Company, China. Wong Huk Kee, August 1960., 152; 1 Map 540 x 760 cm.; 1:11,670; Format: Map; Also contains area maps and indexes.; Access Points: China
- [South & Central China Provinces][Translated from Chinese] by [East Atlas Society][Translated from Chinese]. [East Atlas Society], October 1938., 153; 800 x 1060 cm.; 1:3,200,000; Format: Map; First Printing, October 1938.; 3 Insets: "Pearl Delta Region, "Islands of the South China Sea" & "Communication Map of China and South Asia".; .; Access Points: China
- [Administrative Map of the People's Republic of China][Translated from Chinese] by [New China Map and Atlas Society] [Translatedfrom Chinese]. [Beijing]: [Zhonghua Book Co]., January 1954., 154; 1080 x 1500 cm.; 1:4,000,000; Format: Map; First Printing. Coverage illustrates Situation as of November 1953.; Inset; "South China Islands".; Access Points: China
- Asia and Adjacent Areas by The National Geographical Society. Washington, D.C.: National Geographical Society, 1951., 155; 1230 x 1570 cm.; 1:9,000,000; Two Point Equidistant; Format: Map; Gilbert Grosvenor, Editor.; Access Points: Asia
- China by The National Geographical Society. Washington, D.C.: National Geographical Society, June 1945., 156; 670 x 950 cm.; 1:7,000,000; Albers Conical Equal-Area; Format: Map; Gilbert Grosvenor, Editor.; Access Points: China
- Postal Map of Western Szechwan District by General Bureau of Postal Service. Szechwan, China: General Bureau of Postal Service, April 1942 [Oct. 1942]., 157; 1520 x 1080 cm.; 1:500,000; Format: Map; Insets of Northern Szechwan District, Postal Stations of Sikang Province.; Access Points: China
- People's Republic of China by Map and Atlas Publishing Society [Translated from Chinese]. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, 1966., 158; 540 x 750 cm.; 1:9,000,000; Format: Map; Insets of Islands of South China Sea, China's Neighbors.; Includes some Japanese place names.; Access Points: China
- People's Republic of China by Cartographers Jin Ju'an, Chen Zhifang, Yang Boru. Beijing, China: Asian Light Map Society, November 1950., 159; 770 x 1060 cm.; 1:6,000,000; Lambert; Format: Map; Series sheets: 12th edition; Insets of Islands of South China Sea, Relief Map of P.R.C.; Inset of Administrative Districts of P.R.C.; Access Points: China
- China and [Surrounding Countries & South East Asia} by Cartographers Jin Ju'an, Chen Zhifang, Yang Boru. Beijing, China: Asian Light Map Society, May 1951., 160; 1060 x 760 cm.; 1:8,500,000; Format: Map; Series sheets: 1st edition; Inset of map of Korea.; List of population and areas of countries shown on map.; Access Points: China
- The Wall Map of China by The Great China Book Company. Hong Kong: The Great Chian Book Company, April 1957., 161; 790 x 1080 cm.; 1:6,000,000; Lambert; Format: Map; Series sheets: Revised edition; Insets of Relief Map of China, Islands of South China Seas.; Inset Map of Beijing City and surrounding areas.; Access Points: China
- Map of Taipei City by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Taipei, Taiwan: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, April 25, 1961., 162; 785 x 540 cm.; Format: Map; Tourist map of Taipei.; Access Points: China
- Hunan Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, December 1979., 163; 1060 x 760 cm.; 1:800,000; Format: Map; Insets of Changsha City, Shaoshan District. Mao's birthplace.; Access Points: China
- Guangdong Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, June 1975., 164; 520 x 760 cm.; 1:800,000; Format: Map; Insets of Islands of South China Sea, Guangzhou City.; Access Points: China
- Zhejiang Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, April 1975., 165; 760 x 530 cm.; 1:1,100,000; Format: Map; Inset of Hangzhou City.; Access Points: China
- Fujian Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, September 1978., 166; 1060 x 760 cm.; 1:750,000; Format: Map; Inset of Fuzhou Cit.; Access Points: China
- Shanxi Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, March 1975., 167; 530 x 760 cm.; 1:1,100,000; Format: Map; Inset of Taiyuan City.; Access Points: China
- Liaoning Province by Map and Atlas Publishing Society. Beijing, China: Map and Atlas Publishing Society, January 1977., 168; 530 x 760 cm.; 1:600,000; Format: Map; Inset of Shenyang City.; Access Points: China
- Shaanxi Province by Yechang Yasin Geography Society. Beijing, China: Yechang Yasin Geography Society, October 1937., 169; 760 x 610 cm.; 1:200,000; Format: Map; Insets of Xijing City, Nanzheng City.; Photocopy.; Access Points: China
- Southeast China Costal Relief Map by Map Publishing House. Shanghai, China: Map Publishing House., 170; 1080 x 775 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.; Access Points: China
- Central Yangsze Valley Relief by Map Publishing House. Shanghai, China: Map Publishing House., 171; 1060 x 1100 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.; Access Points: China
- Sichwan Region Relief Map by Map Publishing House. Shanghai, China: Map Publishing House., 172; 1050 x 1550 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.; Access Points: China
- Shanxi, Gansu, Quinghai Relief Map by Map Publishing House. Shanghai, China: Map Publishing House., 173; 1050 x 1550 cm.; 1:1,400,000; Format: Map; Based on Map drawn in 1945 by Shen Bao Press Group.; Access Points: China
- Guangdong Province by Dah Chung Book Co.. Hong Kong, China: Dah Chung Book Co.., 174; 370 x 540 cm.; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; Insets of Hainan Island and coastal area of Guangdong Province.; In English and Chinese.; Access Points: China
- Fujian Province Map of Fujian Province by Dah Chung Book Co.. Hong Kong, China: Dah Chung Book Co.., 175; 370 x 540 cm.; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; In English and Chinese.; Access Points: China
- Map of Qing Dynasty-Daoguang 12 (1832) by Li Zhaoluo. unknown:., 176; 350 x 1325 cm.; Format: Map; In Chinese.; Photocopy.; Access Points: China
- Boundary Map of Chinese and Russian Border, Guangxu 16 (1890) by Hong Jun. unknown:., 177; 450 x 610 cm.; Format: Map; In Chinese.; Photocopy.; Access Points: China Russia
- Lower Yangtze Valley-17th Century by Geography Department, Nanjing University. Nanjing, China:., 178; 740 x 930 cm.; Format: Map; In Chinese.; Photocopy-2 copies.; Access Points: China
- China during Song Dynasty (960-1279) Japan:., 179; 900 x 760 cm.; 1:3,000,000; Format: Map; In Chinese.; Inset maps of China and Formosa (Taiwan).; Access Points: China
- Shanghai City Transportation Map by Shanghai Peoples Publishing House. Shanghai, China: Shanghai Peoples Publishing House, 1975., 180; 520 x 740 cm.; Format: Map; In Chinese-Tourist Map.; Reprinted by Center for Chinese Research Materials, Washington, D.C.; Access Points: China
- Nanking-Shanghai-Hangchow Area, 181; 390 x 560 cm.; 1:400,000; Format: Map; Access Points: China
- [Relief Maps of areas in Gansu, Shanxi, Shaaxi Provinces], 182; 420 x 640 cm.; various; Format: Map; Thematic treatments including main river and tributaries showing soil composition, river bank slopes, river depths, erosion and other land characteristics; Sheets 1-4: Xifeng, Sheets 4-9: Wangjiagou River(Lishan county), Sheets 10-15:Xigou River(Sishan county),Sheets 16-23:Daohuanggou River(Hequ county), Sheets 24-28: Quingyugou River(Yulin county), Sheets 29-35:Shangjugou River(Jingbian county), Sheets; Access Points: China
- Compensating Polar Planimeters with Tracer Point No. 62 0002 by Keuffel & Esser Co.. Morristown, NJ:., 183; 110 x 235 x 70 cm.; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; Three parts, instruction book, and box.
- Stencil Kit, Leroy 3240 by Keuffel & Esser Co.. Morristown, NJ:., 184; 80 x 320 x 42 cm.; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; Fifteen parts and box.
- Compass and Drawing Tools, No. 650 by Alteneder. not shown:., 185; 80 x 170 x 30 cm.; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; Four parts and box.
- Anvil Railroad Pen, 5 1/4 in., No. 932 by Keuffel & Esser Co.. Morristown, NJ:., 186; 40 x 150 x 18 cm.; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; One part and box.
- Four Dividers and Two Stencils by Keuffel & Esser Co. and Esco. Morristown, NJ:., 187; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; Six parts.
- Precison Pantograph Small Type 500 by A. Ott. Bayern, Germany:., 188; 130 x 640 x 70 cm.; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; Ten parts ,instruction book, and box.
- Flexible Curve Rule, Transparent Edge, 12 in. No. N1924-12 by Keuffel & Esser Co.. Morristown, NJ:., 189; 50 x 335 x 20 cm.; Format: Technical Drawing Instruments; Two parts and box.
- Various subjects covering China by Harold Wiens and Students. various: unknown, various., 190; Format: Textual Material; Subjects: Salt Industry in Ming China, The importance of Sui and T'ang Canal Systems, Liao Dynasty, Ming Dynasty, Chian Pre-History, Geography of the Shang, Ch'in, Chou, Sino -Japanese Relations, China Historical Generalizations, continued in Note 2; Post-Han and Five Dynasties, Sui & T'ang, Yung (Mongol), Sung N&S.; Access Points: China
- Economic Geography of Southwest China, (Szechwan, Kweichow, Yunnan) Translated by JPRS by Edited by Sun Ching-chih, Compiled by Sun P'an-shou,Sun Ch'eng-lieh, Shen Wei-ch'eng, and Chang Pei. Washington, D.C.: United States Joint Publications Research Services: 15,069., 191; 740 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Translation.; Loose pages in box.; Access Points: China
- Agricultural Geography of Communist China by Liu Shi-chi. Washington, D.C.: United States Joint Publications Research Services: 8041, April 1961., 192; 29 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Translation.; Access Points: China
- Peasant Families and Agrarian Community in the Process of Economic Development by Shigeru Ishikawa. Bellagio, Italy: The Conference on "Agriculture in Development Theory, May 1973., 193; 55 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Presented at the Conference May 23-29, 1973. in Bellagio, Italy.; Access Points: China
- Structural and Technological Change in the Postwar U.S. Economy: An Input-Output Analysis by Dr. Roger H. Bezdek. Washington, D.C.: United States Energy Research and Development Administration, September 1976., 194; 55 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Presented At the Annual Meeting of the AEA in Atlantic City, NJ.
- Scope for the Substitution of Labor and Equipment in Civil Construction-A Progress Report by World Bank, Prepared by: I.K. Sud, C.G. Harral, and B.P. Coukis. [Washington, D.C.]: Transport Research Div., Transportation Dept., World Bank, July 1976., 195; 28 Pages; Format: Textual Material
- Canton [Published by Kuang-chou Literary Press, Canton 1959, Translated by JPRS] by Communist China, Canton Branch of the Chinese People Association of Foreign Cultural Relations. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Commerce, JPRS: 16,369, November 1962., 196; 86 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Translation.; Access Points: China
- Agricultural Geography of China by Chu Cho. Washington, D.C.: United States. Department of Commerce, JPRS: 16,911, December 1962., 197; 45 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Access Points: China
- Statistical Analysis of Price System in Mainland China by Toshiyuki Mizoguchi. Tokyo, Japan: The Institute of Economic Research, Hitotsubashi Univ. of Tokyo., 198; 11 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Reprint Series No. 14.; Copier pages.; Access Points: China
- China's Agricultural Improvement Program by Raymond T. Moyer. Washington, D.C.: United States Department of Agriculture, Vol.11, No. 10, October 1947., 199; Pages 130-142; Format: Textual Material; Loose pages.; Access Points: China
- The Government and Economy of Manchuria by Chao Kuo-chun. New York, NY: Far Eastern Survey, Vol. 22, No. 13, pages 169-184, December 1953., 200; Pages 169-184; Format: Textual Material; Access Points: Manchuria Japan
- Economic Contrasts: China, India, and Japan by Hugh T. Patrick and Peter Schran. New Haven, CN: Yale University, Economic Growth Center, 1963., 201; Pages 168-184; Format: Textual Material; Reprint from Journal of International Affairs, Vol .17, No. 2, 1963.; Access Points: China
- Foreign and Domestic Debt in Communist China by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, October 1960., 202; 11 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Prepared by George N. Ecklund.; Access Points: China
- Average Annual Money Earnings of Workers and Staff in Communist China 1949-60 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, October 1960., 203; 11 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Access Points: China
- Taxation in Communist China 1950-59 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, July 1961., 204; 117 Pages; Format: Textual Material; Prepared by George N. Ecklund.; Access Points: China
- The Short-Lived Liberal Phase in Economic Thinking in Communist China by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, June 1963., 205; 22 Pages; Format: Textual Material; CIA/RR 63-14.; Access Points: China
- The Program for Water Conservancy in Communist China 1949-61 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1962., 206; 49 Pages; Format: Textual Material; CIA/RR 63-13.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. Methods of Constructing Economic Indexes from Incomplete Data by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, December 1974., 207; 22 Pages; Format: Textual Material; (ER) 74-64.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. People's Republic of China: Foreign Trade in Machinery and Equiptment Since 1952 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, January 1975., 208; 34 Pages; Format: Textual Material; (ER) 75-60.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. Production of Machinery and Equiptment in the Peoples Republic of China by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, May 1975., 209; 31 Pages; Format: Textual Material; (ER) 75-63.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. People's Republic of China: Chemical Fertilizer Supplies, 1949-74 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, August 1975., 210; 20 Pages; Format: Textual Material; A (ER) 75-70.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. Value Added by Work Brigades in Railroad and Highway Construction in China,1952-57 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, November 1975., 211; 11 Pages; Format: Textual Material; 76-10150.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. China's Minerals and Metals Position in the World Market by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, March 1976., 212; 21 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 76-10150.; Access Points: China
- Research Aid. People's Republic of China: Estimated Yuan Value of Foreign Trade In Machinery and Equiptment 1951-73 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, April 1976., 213; 20 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 76-10250.; Access Points: China
- Communist Aid to Less Developed Countries by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, July 1976., 214; 33 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 76-10372U.
- Research Aid. China: The Coal Industry by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, November 1976., 215; 23 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 76-10691.; Access Points: China
- The International Energy Situation: Outlook to 1985 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, April 1977., 216; 18 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 77-10240 U.; Access Points: World
- Prospects for Soviet Oil Production by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, April 1977., 217; 11 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 77-10270.; Map. Major Soviet Petroleum Deposits, Pipelines, Refineries.; Access Points: Russia
- Research Aid. Handbook of Economic Statistics 1977 by Central Intelligence Agency. [Washington, D.C.]: Central Intelligence Agency, September 1977., 218; 165 Pages; Format: Textual Material; ER 77-10537.; Access Points: China